The Green Dolphin Street
Penitentiary, a .k .a. The Aquarium.
Mystery and Power were both
birthed here at some point.
Something which no ordinary people
can see, and for those who can,
the Mystery and Power were both
birthed here at some point.
remain foggy.
Jolene received an additional
five years for attempting to
escape and has been in the
punishment cell for a few weeks now.
Everything will
start after that.
Everything.
But before that happens,
there's something else I
to look into.
It's another prisoner.
One that goes by the
name of Hermes Costello.
It's my understanding that she
and Jolene have already met.
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Wait!
Come back, you bastard!
The medical board?
What the hell?
I don't want
to
play,
let's go!
Shotsieve I want to
dream I don't want to
be free Break out We
don't want too When I'm
McDonald's Break out The
habit of puedo And definitely
Eye-t
awakened
I don't stop beating,
don't stop beating,
don't stop beating a man!
fever.
But the wound has practically disappeared.
Could I have been dreaming?
Wait, don't get ahead of yourself.
I remember it's coming back to me now.
A five-year sentence.
I was in custody for burglary, waiting
to be transferred to this prison.
I picked that thing up in the meeting
room in the jail.
I saw it just sitting there.
But knowing my luck, I cut my hand pretty
bad on it, which totally pissed me off.
Who was it?
What was that woman's name?
Gwess. That's right.
I sold that thing to her.
And that night, I somehow passed out.
And now,
here I am.
Have I really been sleeping since then?
And my wound is mostly healed.
Hmm hey what's the deal with this sticker?
Huh i already peeled off the sticker
that was on the palm of my hand.
Am i remembering this correctly in
1492 columbus sailed the ocean blue?
Bug's bunny's birthday is july
27th 1940 i'm certain of it.
What the Ah!
I thought I'd already thrown it away!
Huh?
My shoes.
Something seems different.
But what...
is it?
There's one, two...
There's three, four, five, and six...
Ouch!
Hold on, now there are five again!
It went back to normal!
Did...
did the high fever cause
astigmatism in my eyes?
But there's that sticker.
That's the sticker that I just took off.
Don't you dare.
That's nasty!
The hell is your problem?
Yeah, why don't you pipe down, new meat?
Uh, don't mind me. Back to sleep.
You moron.
No, this is definitely not an
astigmatism from having a high fever.
I'm definitely touching it.
I feel the weight.
This sticker!
Wherever I place it, it creates
an exact duplicate of the object.
I peel it off.
It causes damage as the
two merge back into one.
And this sticker!
It sounds insane,
but I'm certain it emerged from inside
of my body, from the cut on my hand.
And so, once I accept this new
reality, it may come in handy.
Guccio!
There's no point in overthinking it.
I just have to come to terms with the fact
that the sticker comes out of my hand.
Hey, you!
Give me back my money, you rat!
Huh?
What?
The hell? Gross.
He...
he just walked away from here?
He's trying to pretend
that nothing happened?
I snagged this without thinking,
because it was right there.
Now that I have this thing,
what is it? What's it do?
Looks like you managed
to break your fever.
You're clear to return
to general population.
Okay, but...
That nighttime janitor guy.
What's his name?
Is he an upstanding prisoner?
The doctor has better
things to do with this time!
Bait it!
Who, the night janitor?
The hell would I know?
Nah, I don't know him at all.
It looks like a CD, some kind of disc,
based on its shape and the way it shines.
But I've never seen a disc that
was squishy and elastic like this.
And then, there was another one
of these sticking out of his face.
That makes two discs in total.
What the?
I can see something inside of it.
Now the money that I took from
that sick prisoner is all mine.
What?
I've hidden 5,000 bucks
and nobody has a clue.
What am I watching?
McQueen, my child, do you think you
can lend me a hand with something?
A little something between friends.
So what do you say?
What the hell did that thing just show me?
It was like I was
watching someone's memory!
So, word's gotten round.
You've been asking
people all about me, huh?
I have prior experience in
stalking, but I've got to say,
I've never been stalked by a woman before.
Yeah, this is a first.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Answer me!
Didn't you eject some
discs out of your face?
Sorry, Discs.
I can't remember.
What's going on?
I'm so pathetic.
I can't remember.
Hey, why'd you bust out
crying all of a sudden?
You took money from me while I was unconscious
in sickbay this morning, stupid ass.
Money?
That sounds right.
I had thousands of dollars
stashed away in a safe place,
but now I have no memory of anyone!
Damn, are you sure you're
all right there, man?
You better not be messing with me.
Did you just ask me if I'm all right?
You're so kind.
It's been forever since the last
time I spoke with a woman. Huh?
Well, it's my first time.
My first time to have a
heart-to-heart conversation with
a woman as staggeringly beautiful
as you are and very happy, honestly.
Someday I hope to meet
a girl like you and get
the chance to live
happily together with her.
Huh?
Of course, that won't happen
because I'm a pathetic loser.
And why would you want someone like that?
It's also pointless.
I feel like dying.
Wait!
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
No!
Oh, God!
Who is this guy?
Hey, McQueen.
You are truly evil in a
misanthrope, aren't you?
You worm your way through
this world with no animosity,
and worst of all, you don't even think
you're causing anyone any trouble.
You also insist on playing the victim
although you have no interest in others.
You're hoping that someone will come
along one of these days and save you.
You're what's referred to in certain
circles as the worst dragging others down
with your misfortune is a truly evil
approach which makes me have to say I'm
quite fond of you McQueen if you were
to come across my enemy when you're
moving about this prison you'd be sure
to get rid of them for me like a true Oh,
friend,
isn't that right, McQueen?
Help me!
Belt is around his neck,
and this around mine!
Help me, please, somebody!
I'm passing out!
Maybe if I can bring him down,
his power will release me as well!
Sticker!
He has a strange ability like mine.
That means I wasn't the only one. Damn it!
What the hell's wrong with you?
Why'd you hang yourself like that?
Did you really just help me?
Thank you.
You're a real lifesaver.
Who the hell do you
think you are, asshole?
And why the hell do you keep
dragging me into your problems?
You have some power too, right?
Don't lie to me.
My power I don't know what you're
talking about but that'll be okay.
I won't ever do that again.
I'm fully awake now.
I really owe you everything
for saving my life.
I swear I'll repay you
for your kindness one day.
Oh I couldn't just sit
back and let you do it.
You don't have to worry
about the scars
on his wrist.
He's tried to commit suicide
before and I don't think
he's realized his ability
affects those around him.
Yet he's bad news.
My posture is even the same as his.
Oh God, I drifted even
further away from him!
You dumb jerk!
You asshole!
The disc.
I have no idea what any of this is about.
But it must have something
to do with that disc!
Please let me die.
I said I would pay you back, but a piece
of trash like me can't do anything.
The last thing I want
to do is be your friend.
I'll never save your life again.
In fact, you come near me
again, I'll kill you myself.
Just kill me already.
If I was going to be Vernon, I'd
want it to be someone like you.
Hold on.
I think I just saw her pull a
disc out of the toilet bowl.
For some reason, I feel
like that belongs to me.
Will she give it back to me?
I guess not.
She probably won't do it.
Hey, let me through!
My discharge permit!
Now, let me through!
Damn it!
I have to get as far away from
that guy as I possibly can.
I should get going.
Back to my cell.
I was right.
Your power has awakened.
I can help you.
I can explain these new abilities to you.
What you have is called a stand power.
Stand wielders are drawn
to each other like magnets.
It's just a part of the whole phenomenon.
No one's sure why.
But that's why you met him.
That sad janitor.
Wait, what's a kid doing here?
Unless I'm mistaken, you're the
one who sold Jolene's pendant.
That's the reason why.
She asked me to keep an eye on you
in case anything suspicious happened.
Jolene, huh?
Did she get mixed up in all of this?
The villain who steals people's hearts.
He's an enemy to both myself and Jolene.
We're searching for
the hearts he's stolen.
Stolen heart?
The one responsible
for this is Pale Snake.
If you know anything about
it, I ask you to help us.
These stolen hearts is
this disc what you're
talking about is that it
came out of that janitor?
Maybe you should start
with what this thing is
hold on didn't he have
two discs another one?
Oh yeah you're right
memory disc and stand disc
it comes in a set of two
two discs make a single
Soul if we can track
down the second one we
might be able to find out
who's behind pale snake?
It can't be there's no way
is that jerk still trying
to mess with me this is crazy
i ran so Far away from him
no what's
happening it's
electricity their rotten pastor
janitor must Be electrocuting
himself it's over i don't
think he's done you can't
kill a human being just by
Sending a hundred volts of
electricity onto their exposed
skin that's not how it works
It's all due to electrical
resistance that's why it stopped
he failed to kill himself
However if he's still planning
to try electrocuting himself
again then i'm thinking He's
probably looking for salt water.
With salt water, the current
conductivity will be almost 100%.
Electricity can pierce and burn the
heart completely at those levels.
They use salt water for IVs and a
bunch of other healthcare stuff.
There's plenty of it
down in the medical wing.
I can't go any further than this.
There are too many other prisoners
roaming that floor right now.
I gotta beat his ass unconscious and
take out the other disc when it ejects!
It's my only chance!
Whoa! Hold on! Just listen! Take a look.
You see what's happened to my left arm?
It's burnt and cut, just like your arm!
Are you starting to get the picture?
I don't know how, but you
have a strange ability?
where whatever injuries you sustain
while trying to offer yourself,
the same injuries happen to me, too!
So stop thinking about suicide!
I'm sure things will turn around
with good times waiting for you!
You think so?
Four years ago, I was just
doing some cleaning. Huh?
I was in my apartment,
cleaning and oiling my shotgun.
Somehow, a shell had gotten
itself stuck in the gun's barrel.
It was an accident!
My room was on the 10th floor.
That's when a woman jumped from the 11th
floor in an attempt to kill herself.
It's a matter of luck.
People win millions in the lottery, so
obviously the opposite has to happen, right?
She was supposed to hit the
ground and die from suicide.
But instead,
everyone assumes that I shot and
killed that woman up on the 11th floor.
The judge even called me cold-hearted
before he threw the book at me.
That's the man you've
seen before you! Wait!
You like panties, right?
Has anyone ever given you a pair?
If a cute girl were to give you her
panties, you'd feel lucky, right?
Huh?
Sure, you're going through
some tough times right now.
But if you were given
freshly worn panties,
and that means your luck
can change for the better,
even at the worst of times, when things
seem their darkest, don't you see?
Oh!
How embarrassing!
But I'll give them to you!
The actual pair I'm
wearing right this second!
You really want to give them to me?
Of course!
I made a promise, didn't I? But listen,
everybody hates when the weekend is over
and Monday's right around the corner.
But we all think a fun
Saturday is waiting for me
at the other end of this
tunnel and live our lives,
because we know it's not
always going to be a Monday.
The day I got arrested was a Saturday.
It's strange.
You're saying something good that
gives me courage, which I appreciate.
But maybe you're using
all those fine-sounding
words because you're
trying to save yourself,
right?
Well, it's part of it.
See, you're acting like you care,
but you're actually just trying
to calm me down for the moment.
The words you speak are
not sincere, are they?
So that's how you treat me.
I should have known
this all from the start.
No one wants to be with Trash,
but I'm worse than Trash.
My presence is invisible.
You couldn't even find me
to throw me away properly!
Whoa!
Pump the brakes, man. Okay.
I'll admit that the only reason I talk
to you is because I want to survive this.
Right.
I have to make you see.
This pale snake son of a
bitch is only using you.
He's taking advantage
of your broken heart.
But if you stop thinking about
suicide, nothing will happen.
He won't have power over you anymore.
Maybe then you'll stop thinking
only about your damn self!
Which is exactly what
you need, you shit stain!
You're so great.
I mean it.
Your heart spoke to me.
You have me feeling so inspired now.
It really shows a guy
just how lucky he is.
I'm getting the chance to meet an amazing
person such as yourself
right before the end.
And for that, I'd like to thank you.
If
I can make sure to die with you,
then we can stay together forever.
I never realized Please,
I can't be so happy!
That evil little prick.
He really has to be the most lonesome,
corrupt son of a bitch I've ever met.
I'm not gonna be lonely anymore!
Asshole!
Don't even think about
hitting that button!
That was too close, that damned idiot.
I was able to put a sticker on him.
The sparks from the
electricity should burn it off.
And when the sticker is burned off,
then the object that the sticker split
in two is going to merge back together.
Damn it, the shock made me remember.
This moron hid a bunch of
money around here somewhere.
Five grand.
I'll take that money as
payment, you asshole.
And as for you, pale snake, I
suffered a lot because of you.
What the hell are you scheming?
I need to see her.
I've got questions, Jolene Cujo.
Of some place
other than here?
Although you think I smile!
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny.
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far
from today?
Thank you.